BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IX: Industry Code #44, Retail
  - Meat Cutters (retail), 1934-1939 (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Item 4: Butcher's Board of Trade of San Francisco and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 115, Western Federation of Butchers of California, 1935-1936; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 4/17/1935 and expires on 4/16/1936. Covers 608 workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 5: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 88, AFL, 1935-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1935 and expires on 8/31/1937. Covers 1100 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 6: Salesmen and Poultry Workers Union of Greater New York, Local 662, AFL, 1935-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 11/15/1935 and expires on 12/15/1937. Covers 400 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 7: Kroger Grocery Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 73, AFL, 1935-1936; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1935 and expires on 9/30/1936. Covers an unknown number of workers in Milwaukee, WI
    - Item 8: Kroger Grocery Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 73, AFL, 1935-1936; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Item 9: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 610, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1936 and expires on 1/1/1937. Covers 440 workers in Cincinnati, OH
    - Item 10: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 653, AFL, Minnesota State Federation of Labor, Minneapolis Central Labor Union, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1936 and expires on 7/1/1937. Covers 1050 workers in Minneapolis, MN
    - Item 11: J. M. McKelvey Company, Geo L. Oles, Lloyd Market, and others and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 200, AFL, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1936 and expires on 7/1/1937. Covers 65 workers in Youngstown, OH
    - Item 12: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 73, AFL, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1936 and expires on 9/30/1937. Covers an unknown number of workers in Milwaukee, WI
    - Item 13: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 233, AFL, Central Trades and Labor Council, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1936 and expires on 1/1/1937. Covers 168 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 14: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 342, AFL, Central Trades and Labor Council, Butchers District Council of the Metropolitan District, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1936 and expires on 1/1/1937. Covers an unknown number of workers in Brooklyn, NY
    - Item 15: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 534, AFL, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1936 and expires on 10/31/1937. Covers 262 workers in East St. Louis, IL
    - Item 16: Salesmen and Poultry Workers Union of Greater New York, Local 662, AFL, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 11/15/1936 and expires on 11/15/1937. Covers 445 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 17: Ye Olde New York Branch and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 665, AFL, Central Trades and Labor Council, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 5/31/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 18: Salesmen and Poultry Workers Union of Greater New York, Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 370, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 1/1/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 19: Bellingham Meat Dealers Association and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 247, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 11/1/1938. Covers 165 workers in Bellingham, WA
    - Item 20: Joe Ackley, Louis Allen, Vern Warrell, and others and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 529, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1937 and expires on 4/1/1938. Covers 70 workers in Yakima, WA
    - Item 21: Retail and Wholesale Fish, Oyster and Poultry Dealers Association and Fish and Oyster Workers Union, Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 649, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1937 and expires on 6/1/1938. Covers 110 workers in Portland, OR
    - Item 22: Washington Heights Branch, New York State Association of Retail Meat Dealers and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 665, AFL, Central Trades and Labor Council, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1937 and expires on 5/31/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 23: Retail and Wholesale Fish, Oyster and Poultry Dealers Association and Fish and Oyster Workers Union, Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 649, AFL, 1937-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 6/2/1937 and expires on 6/2/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in Portland, OR
    - Item 24: Eugene Retail Meat Dealers and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 324, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1937 and expires on 7/1/1938. Covers 35 workers in Eugene, OR
    - Item 25: Chicago Retail Meat Dealers Association and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 320, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 10/30/1937 and expires on 10/30/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 26: Hebrew Butcher Workers Union of Greater New York, Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 234, AFL, Central Trades and Labor Council, United Hebrew Trades, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 11/15/1937 and expires on 10/15/1938. Covers 1100 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 27: Santa Barbara, California Master Butchers and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 556, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1938 and expires on 1/1/1939. Covers 105 workers in Santa Barbara, CA
    - Item 28: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 229, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 8/29/1938 and expires on 12/31/1939. Covers 500 workers in San Diego, CA
    - Item 29: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 421, AFL, California State Federation of Labor, Los Angeles Central Labor Council, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 12/3/1938 and expires on 12/3/1939. Covers 2200 workers in Los Angeles, CA
    - Item 30: Retail Meat Dealers Association and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 151, AFL, 1939-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1939 and expires on 12/31/1939. Covers 75 workers in Everett, WA
    - Item 31: Sholar's Markets, Safeway Stores, Whelden's, and others and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of NA, Local 193, AFL, California State Federation of Labor, Southern California Conference of Butchers, Taft and Bakersfield Central Labor Councils, 1939-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1939 and expires on 12/31/1939. Covers 100 workers in Bakersfield, CA
  - Meat Cutters (retail), 1936-1939 (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 266, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 7/16/1936 and expires on 7/16/1937. Covers an unknown number of workers in Santa Cruz, CA
    - Item 2: Master Butcher of Chicago, National Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 320, AFL, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1936 and expires on 9/30/1937. Covers 185 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 3: Retail Meat Dealers Association of Chicago and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 320, AFL 1936), 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 10/30/1936 and expires on 10/30/1937. Covers 130 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 4: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 573, AFL 1937), 1937-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 1/1/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in Greensburg, PA
    - Item 5: Retail and Wholesale Butchers and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 181, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 11/14/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Shreveport, LA
    - Item 6: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 12, AFL, Minnesota State Federation of Labor, Duluth Trades and Labor Assembly, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 6/9/1938. Covers 75 workers in Duluth, MN
    - Item 7: Shinners Meat Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 612, AFL, Illinois State Federation of Labor, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 10/1/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Joliet, IL
    - Item 8: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 532, Western Federation of Butchers, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 1/1/1938. Covers 200 workers in Vallejo, CA
    - Item 9: Bazley Markets, Toth Delane Market, Toth Packing House, and others and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 200, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 12/31/1938. Covers 275 workers in Youngstown, OH
    - Item 10: Retail Butchers of Tracy and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 654, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 1/1/1938. Covers 21 workers in Tracy, CA
    - Item 11: Cleveland Retail Meat Dealers Association and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 427, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 1/19/1937 and expires on 3/10/1938. Covers 1000 workers in Cleveland, OH
    - Item 12: Poultry Schochtim Union of Greater New York, Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 370, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 2/2/1937 and expires on 2/1/1938. Covers 330 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 13: Bronx Branch and Brooklyn Branch, New York State Association of Retail Meat Dealers and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 233, AFL, 1937-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 6/17/1937 and expires on 6/16/1940. Covers 2000 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 14: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 546, AFL, Illinois Federation of Labor, Chicago Federation of Labor, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 9/22/1937 and expires on 9/30/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 15: Detroit Retail Meat Merchants and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 539, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1937 and expires on 8/1/1938. Covers 80 workers in Detroit, MI
    - Item 16: Meat Cutters (retail), 1936- 1939 (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Item 17: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 73, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1937 and expires on 9/30/1938. Covers 750 workers in Milwaukee, WI
    - Item 18: Retail Meat Dealers Association, Master Butchers Association and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 143, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 10/4/1937 and expires on 10/4/1938. Covers 700 workers in Portland, OR
    - Item 19: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 538, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 10/6/1937 and expires on 10/6/1938. Covers 37 workers in Janesville, WI
    - Item 20: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 285, AFL, Minnesota State Federation of Labor, Hibbing Central Labor Union, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 11/10/1937 and expires on 5/1/1938. Covers 28 workers in Hibbing, MN
    - Item 21: Retail Meat Dealers Association and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 547, AFL, Chicago Federation of Labor, Illinois State Federation of Labor, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 12/14/1937 and expires on 9/30/1938. Covers 183 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 22: Sale Packing Company, Farmer's Exchange, Teefey Poultry Company, and others and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 534, AFL, 1938-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 3/31/1938 and expires on 3/31/1938. Covers 39 workers in East St. Louis, IL
    - Item 23: Live Poultry Protective Association and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 177, AFL, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1938 and expires on 4/1/1939. Covers 50 workers in Newark, NJ
    - Item 24: Quaker Cash Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 372, AFL, 1938-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 5/4/1938 and expires on 9/30/1938. Covers 50 workers in Akron, OH
    - Item 25: Brockelman Brothers, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 407, AFL, Central Labor Union, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 5/5/1938 and expires on 5/6/1939. Covers 590 workers in Worcester, MA
    - Item 26: Lake Erie Provision Company, Ohio Provision Company, Theurer- Norton Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 500, AFL, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1938 and expires on 10/1/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in Cleveland, OH
    - Item 27: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 555, AFL, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 10/27/1938 and expires on 10/27/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in Washington, DC
    - Item 28: Stahl-Meyer, Inc. and Butchers Union of Greater New York, Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 174, AFL, 1939-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 5/14/1939 and expires on 10/1/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 29: Meat Cutters (retail), 1936- 1939 (Box 130, Folder 15)
  - Meat Cutters (retail), 1938-1939 (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Safeway Stores and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 570, AFL, 1937-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1937 and expires on 11/1/1939. Covers 131 workers in Fort Worth, TX
    - Item 2: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 587, AFL, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 9/7/1938 and expires on 9/7/1939. Covers 250 workers in Santa Monica, CA
    - Item 3: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 606, AFL, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 9/15/1938 and expires on 9/15/1939. Covers 50 workers in El Paso, TX
    - Item 4: Retail Meat Dealer Association of Chicago and Cook County and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 546, AFL, Illinois Federation of Labor, Chicago Federation of Labor, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 10/24/1938 and expires on 9/30/1939. Covers 6000 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 5: Kroger, Liberty Cash Store, Easy Way Stores and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 452, AFL, Tennessee Federation of Labor, Memphis Trade and Labor Council, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1938 and expires on 10/31/1939. Covers 300 workers in Memphis, TN
    - Item 6: Ash Brothers Grocery, A. Grund Inc., Busch and Casey, and others and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 608 AFL, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 11/15/1938 and expires on 11/15/1939. Covers 75-85 workers in Goose Creek, TX
    - Item 7: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 608 AFL, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Item 8: Minneapolis Retail Meat Dealers Association and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 653, AFL, Minnesota State Federation of Labor, Minneapolis Central Labor Union, 1939-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 2/14/1939 and expires on 11/1/1939. Covers 900 workers in Minneapolis, MN
  - Meat Cutters (retail), 1938-1940 (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Safeway Stores Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL, 1935-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1935 and expires on 4/1/1940. Covers an unknown number of workers in United States
    - Item 2: Bronx Branch, New York State Association of Retail Meat Dealers and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 233, AFL, 1937-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1937 and expires on 3/31/1940. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 3: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 81, AFL, 1938-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1938 and expires on 2/1/1940. Covers 900 workers in Seattle, WA
    - Item 4: Butchers' Board of Trade of San Francisco and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 115, AFL, Western Federation of Butchers of California, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 3/20/1938 and expires on 3/20/1939. Covers 1000 workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 5: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 226, AFL, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1939 and expires on 1/1/1940. Covers 6 workers in Macon, GA
    - Item 6: Washington Co-operative Egg and Poultry Association, Puget Egg Packers and Pioneer Quality Egg Producers and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 247, AFL, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1939 and expires on 1/1/1940. Covers 250 workers in Bellingham, WA
    - Item 7: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 657, AFL, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 3/1/1939 and expires on 3/1/1940. Covers 265 workers in Miami, FL
    - Item 8: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 213, AFL, American Central Labor Union, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 3/15/1939 and expires on 9/20/1940. Covers 29 workers in Savannah, GA
    - Item 9: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 513, AFL, Birmingham Trades Council, Alabama State Federation of Labor, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 3/23/1939 and expires on 3/23/1940. Covers 132 workers in Birminghman, AL
    - Item 10: Beaty Store, Adams, Brendels, and others and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 259, AFL, 1940-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1940 and expires on 1/1/1941. Covers an unknown number of workers in St. Louis, MO
  - Meat Cutters (retail), 1937-1940 (Box 130, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 425, AFL, 1937-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 7/6/1937 and expires on 7/6/1940. Covers 22 workers in Fort Smith, AR
    - Item 2: National Association of Retail Meat Dealers, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, 1937-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 8/12/1937 and expires on 1/1/1940. Covers an unknown number of workers in Chicago, IL